Guide to the Johan Kugelberg punk collection, circa 1974-1986.
Kugelberg, Johan punk collection
- Series II. Fliers and Posters
  - Professionals, The, 1982; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 24)
    Main text: Friday April 30th 8 PM - At Florentine Gardens - The Professionals feature ex-Sex Pistols Paul Cook and Steve Jones
  - Provo-Anarchistenblad, 1970-1980s; 34 x 21.5 cm. (Box 27, Folder 3)
    Location: Amsterdam, Netherlands
    Main text: Provo is uit!
    Notes: Dutch provo/anarchist flier.
  - Public Image Ltd., 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 24)
    Venue: Olympic Auditorium and Stardust Ballroom
    Location: Los Angeles and Hollywood, CA
    Additional bands or artists: Butthole Surfers, S[ocial] D[istortion], Black Athletes, Samhain, Necros, Jody Foster's Army, Rigor Mortis Concemned to Death
    Main text: Goldenvoice - Nov. 16 - PIL - 1984 - Public Image Limited …
    Notes: Two 8.5 x 5.5 in. fliers on a single sheet, top and bottom; may have been issued both together and separately.
  - Public Image Ltd., 8.5 x 5.5 in. (Box 9, Folder 24)
    Additional bands or artists: Butthole Surfers, S[ocial] D[istortion], Black Athletes
    Notes: The top section only of the double flier above.
  - Punks Unite!, 1980s; 8.5 x 5.5 in. (Box 9, Folder 24)
    Venue: 4th & Wall Sts.
    Main text: Punks Unite! … Big meeting 4 al punks ois & hardcores at 4th & Wall in L.A. … no bands are playing so bring your ghetto blaster 2 the ghetto
  - Queen Elizabeth featuring Wayne County, 1978; 8.5 x 14 in. (Box 27, Folder 3)
    Main text: Anton Perich presents Queen Elizabeth featuring Wayne County the Wonder Woman with a host of performers in a Saturday night dance and video
  - Ramones, 1984; 8.5 x 5.5 in. (Box 9, Folder 24)
    Venue: Pomona Valley Auditorium
    Additional bands or artists: Agent Orange, Chardon Square
    Main text: Olea productions presents Ramones - Gent Orange - Chardon Square
  - Raw (comic), 1984; 8.5 x 14 in. (Box 27, Folder 3)
    Artist: Kaz
    Main text: Read Yourself Raw
  - Readymades, The, 1979-1984; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 24)
    Venue: The Old Waldorf
    Additional bands or artists: Little Rodger & the Dots, The Psychotic Pineapple
    Main text: The Readymades, Little Rodger & the Dots, The Psychotic Pineapple - Let's have a dance party
  - Really Red, 1983; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 24)
    Venue: Metropolis
    Additional bands or artists: Mr. Epp, the Fastbacks
    Main text: From Texas - Really Red with special guests Mr. Epp and the Fastbacks - Metropolis
  - Redd Kross, 1983; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 24)
    Venue: Ascot Grand Prix
    Location: Gardena, CA
    Additional bands or artists: Mood of Defiance, Modern Torture, Nip Drivers
    Main text: A new club opens its doors!! - Red Kross, Mood of Defiance, Modern Torture, Nip Drivers (and big screen videos)
  - Rollins, Henry, 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 24)
    Artist: [David?] Arnoff (photo)
    Venue: Fetish
    Additional bands or artists: Lydia Lunch
    Main text: "Why You Murder Me" productions present… Rollins/Lunch vs. You!!
    Notes: "Music theatre literature performance"
  - Roomates, The, 1980s; 8.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 9, Folder 24)
    Additional bands or artists: The Lewd, Wrong Bros.
    Main text: After Bammie Fab Mabie party - after the farce go to the real thing
  - Rough Trade, ca. 1970s; 23.25 x 16.5 in. (Box 40)
    Venue: Rough Trade
    Main text: Sides are determined by conditions … Rough Trade, 202 Kensington Pk. Rd., W.11.
    Notes: Detournement fumetti poster issued by the record store Rough Trade.
  - Rubber City Rebels, 1979; 8.5 x 11.5 in. (Box 9, Folder 24)
    Venue: The Troubadour
    Main text: Invasion of the Rubber City Rebels
  - Rude Kids, The, 1978-1980; 23.25 x 16.5 in. (Box 40)
    Location: Sweden
    Main text: The Rude Kids - Christina Nilssons Produktions …
    Notes: General promotional poster for Swedish punk band The Rude Kids.
  - Runaways, The, 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 24)
    Location: North Hollywood, CA
    Main text: You are invited to a special party honoring L.A.'s own teen queens of noise! … The Runaways
  - Saccharine Trust, The, 1980s; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 25)
    Artist: Shawn Kerri
    Venue: Moose Lodge
    Additional bands or artists: Atoms, Anti, Red Scare, 51st State, Section 8, Bad Example, Ill Repute
    Main text: Saccharine Trust - Atoms - Anti - with Red Scare and 51st State - Section 8 - Bad Example - Ill Repute
  - Saccharine Trust, The, 1983; 8.5 x 5.25 in. (Box 9, Folder 25)
    Additional bands or artists: Dead Hippie, Nip Drivers, The Patriots
    Main text: Saccharine Trust, Dead Hippie, Nip Drivers, the Patriots - There are no definitive answers here
  - Saint Vitus, 1980-1983; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 25)
    Venue: Anti Club
    Main text: Saint Vitus - July 2 - Wed.
  - Saints, The, ca. 1976; 30.5 x 20 in. (Box 40)
    Main text: (I'm) Stranded - The Saints
    Notes: Promotional poster issued by Harvest/EMI for the Saints' album (I'm) Stranded
  - Salvation Army, 1982; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 25)
    Main text: Peace (and luv) Sunday - Salvation Army in-store!
    Notes: Flier for in-store appearance by the band Salvation Army.
  - Salvation Army, 1982; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 25)
    Venue: The Sweetwater
    Additional bands or artists: The Plugz
    Main text: Having a psych-out with the Salvation Army and the Plugz
  - Samhain, 1984; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 25)
    Venue: Stardust Ballroom
    Additional bands or artists: The Necros, Jody Foster's Army, Condemned to Death, Rigor Mortis
    Main text: Goldenvoice goes to you-know-where for a deadly double-headed pre-turkey blow-out
    Notes: Same flier content as the lower half of the Public Image Ltd. 11/16/84 double-flier above, at full 8.5 x 11 size.
  - Samuelson, Rodney, 1981; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 25)
    Venue: Cal Arts
    Location: Valencia, CA
    Main text: Post-punk art by Rodney S. - A closing party - Hardcore music and free beer provided
    Notes: Flier for an art show by the artist Rodney S[amuelson] (b. 1960).
  - Screamers, The, 1979; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 25)
    Additional bands or artists: Tuxedomoon, The Units
    Main text: A nite of electro psycho rock with the Screamers, Tuxedomoon … and the units
    Notes: Double-sided flier; verso contains press clippings on Screamers and Tuxedomoon.
  - Screamers, The, 1977; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 25)
    Artist: Evenson
    Main text: Screamers & Dead Beats - 10pm Sun & Mon December 18 & 19
  - Secret Hate, 1980s; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 25)
    Venue: On Club
    Additional bands or artists: Minutemen, Angst
    Main text: On club - Secret Hate, Minutemen
  - Secret Hate, 1982; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 25)
    Additional bands or artists: Crewd, Shattered Faith
    Main text: Secret Hate, Crewd, Shattered Faith and more
  - Secret Hate, 1982; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 25)
    Additional bands or artists: Crewd
    Main text: Secret Hate, Crewd - Modern Protest Young Amerikans
  - Secret Hate, 1982; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 25)
    Venue: Galaxy Roller Rink
    Additional bands or artists: Anti, Crewd, Convicted
    Main text: Diaz Productions Present: A "Fight for Freedom" benefit - Secret Hate and Anti with Crewd and Convicted
  - Sex Pistols, 13.25 x 10 in. (Box 27, Folder 3)
    Venue: Leona Theatre
    Location: Pittsburgh, PA
    Main text: WYDD announces the Sex Pistols first US appearance
    Notes: Wheatpasted poster mounted on construction paper.
  - Sex Pistols, ca. 1976-1977; 42.5 x 30 cm. (Box 27, Folder 3)
    Artist: [Jamie Reid]
    Main text: Sex Pistols
    Notes: The first Sex Pistols poster; printed by Jamie Reid/Suburban Press.
  - Sex Pistols, ca. 1976-1977; 43 x 30 cm. (Box 27, Folder 3)
    Main text: Anarchy in the U.K.: Sex Pistols
    Notes: Poster printed by Jamie Reid/Suburban Press.
  - Sex Pistols, 42 x 30 cm. (Box 27, Folder 3)
    Artist: Jamie Reid
    Venue: Brunel University
    Main text: Never mind the bans: Sex Pistols will play
    Notes: Signed by Reid with a certificate of authenticity. A double-sided poster with details of the Pistols' Anarch in the UK tour.
  - Sex Pistols, 1976-1977; 10 x 36.5 in. (Mapcase-folder 1)
    Artist: [Jamie Reid?]
    Main text: God Save the Queen
    Notes: Banner poster, likely issued in conjunction with the "Sex Pistols" logo banner in the same style.
  - Sex Pistols, ca. 1976-1977; 6.25 x 19 in. (Box 30, Folder 1)
    Notes: Small banner with Sex Pistols logo.
  - Sex Pistols, 1977; 16.5 x 22.75 in. (Box 30, Folder 2)
    Additional bands or artists: Eagles
    Main text: Sex Pistols [and] Eagles
    Notes: Double-sided poster issued (folded) by the Swedish fanzine Poster: the Sex Pistols on one side, the Eagles on the other.
  - Sex Pistols, The, 1976; A4 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    Venue: Notre Dame Hall
    Main text: Londons Outrage! Sex Pistols on stage!! At last!
    Notes: This flier was the source image for the cover to Jon Savage's fanzine London's Outrage! #1.
  - Sex Pistols, The, 1976; A4 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    Venue: 100 Club
    Additional bands or artists: The Damned
    Main text: Sex Pistols - Tuesday July 6th - 100 Club - Sex Pistols + the Damned
  - Sex Pistols, The, 1981; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 25)
    Venue: 5112 Wilshire
    Main text: The Great Rock 'n' Roll Swindle … the film that incriminates its audience …
    Notes: Flier for Los Angeles screenings of the Sex Pistols film.
  - Sex Pistols, The, ca. 1980; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 25)
    Venue: High Times
    Additional bands or artists: Generation X, X-Ray Spex, Sham 69, Rich Kids, Terry and the Idiots
    Main text: High Times presents the first annual Ash Wednesday screening of D.O.A. starring Sex Pistols …
    Notes: Flier for screening of a work print of the Sex Pistols film D.O.A. No place specified, but presumably at the High Times editorial office.
  - Sex Pistols, The, ca. Jan. 1978; A4 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    Main text: No future for you!!! - So says johnny Rotten and it's not all lies …
    Notes: Religious anti-Sex Pistols flier.
  - Shattered Faith, 1980s; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 25)
    Artist: R. Mooe/Hinge
    Venue: The Front
    Main text: Shattered Faith - Look out San Diego
  - Shattered Faith, 1982; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 25)
    Venue: Union Theatre
    Additional bands or artists: Sin 34, Anti, Instigator, Decry, Pepsi Challenge, Minutemen, Mood of Defiance, Invisible Chains, Hari-Kari, Zurich 1916, Red Scare
    Main text: Sat. Oct. 2 - Shattered Faith, Sin 34, Anti
  - Silvertones, 1980; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 25)
    Additional bands or artists: The Lewd, Social Unrest, Witnesses, C'est La Guerre
    Main text: Classified - USF Foghorn Escapades Benefit - Silvertones …
  - Sin 34, 1984; 8.5 x 5.5 in. (Box 9, Folder 25)
    Additional bands or artists: The Stains, Urban Gurrillas, Crewd, Detinators, Decry, Battalion of Saints, Power Trip, SVDB, Legal Weapon
    Main text: Next terrorist target? Fri 7/29 - Sin-34, Stains …
  - Skins 'n' Sharps [exhibit], 23.25 x 16.5 in. (Box 30, Folder 2)
    Venue: Dante's Gallery Upstairs
    Location: Fitzroy, [Australia]
    Main text: Sam Biondo in association with Rohan Pugh present Skins 'n' Sharps: The Forgotten Subculture, Melbourne 1971 to 1979
    Notes: Poster for an exhibition.
  - Sleepers, 1978; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 25)
    Additional bands or artists: Fear, The Strays
    Main text: Sleepers - Introducing Fear - Plus the Strays
  - Social Distortion, 1981; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 25)
    Additional bands or artists: Bad Religion, Overkill, Minutemen, The Abandend, Social Dismay
    Main text: Social Distortion, Bad Religion, Overkill, Minutemen …
  - Social Distortion, 1983; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 25)
    Venue: HJ's Rock and Roll Orphanage
    Additional bands or artists: Killroy, The Strike, Beast of Beast
    Main text: Sunday June 12 - Social Distortion, Killroy, The Strike …
  - Social Distortion, 1983; 8.5 x 5.5 in. (Box 9, Folder 25)
    Venue: Boss Hoggs
    Additional bands or artists: Mad Parade, Catch 22
    Main text: New album debut party "Mommys Little Monster" - Social Distortion, Made Parade and Catch 22 …
  - Social Distortion, 1981; 8.5 x 5.5 in. (Box 9, Folder 25)
    Additional bands or artists: Youth Brigade, Hugh Beaumont Experience
    Main text: From California - Social Distortion and Youth Brigade …
  - Soft Boys, ca. 1984; 16.5 x 11.5 in. (Box 27, Folder 3)
    Artist: David Jeffery
    Main text: Give it to the Soft Boys
    Notes: Poster from Raw Records advertising Soft Boys EP.
  - Specials, The, 1980; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 25)
    Location: n.p. [US]
    Main text: The Specials - See something really special! See the Specials on Saturday Nite Live April 19th.
    Notes: Promotional flier issued by Chrysalis Records in connection with The Specials' appearance on SNL.
  - Statics, The, 1984; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 25)
    Main text: Statics, Negative Trend, Ointment - Mon Feb 27 11pm
  - Steel Pulse, 1978; A4 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    Venue: Alexandria Park
    Main text: Northern Carnival!! Against the Nazis - Steel Pulse, Buzzcocks, China Street …
    Notes: Double-sided flier. Event organized by the Anti-Nazi League, Rock Against Racism, and North West Committee Against Racism.
  - Stingers, The, 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 25)
    Venue: Hong Kong Café
    Additional bands or artists: The Speed Queens, The Adolescence [i.e. Adolescents?]
    Main text: What are the greatest hazards at these ages? Complete satisfaction … Hong Kong - Security in a very insecure world
  - Stranglers, The, 1981; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 25)
    Venue: The Stone and Keystone
    Location: [San Francisco?] and Palo Alto, CA
    Main text: Don't miss the Stranglers
  - Subhumans, 1977-1983; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 25)
    Venue: Contempo
    Additional bands or artists: Social Distortion, Saccharine Trust, Youth Brigade
    Main text: Subhumans - Social Distortion, Saccharine Trust, Youth Brigade
  - Subhumans, 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 25)
    Artist: MCM
    Venue: Zeros
    Location: Fort Worth, TX
    Additional bands or artists: Enemy
    Main text: Zeros New Wave Lounge - Tonight's card … Enemy with Bobby Soxx vs. - main event - The Subhumans - from Canada
  - Subterranean, 1981; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 25)
    Venue: Subterranea (record store)
    Additional bands or artists: Nervous Gender, Animal Things, Ghouls, Wolvarines, Jars, Lewd, Jars, Flipper, Black Flag, Woundz, Target Video, Revenge, ALA, Naked Lady Wrestlers, Breakouts
    Main text: 4/11 Sat. Animal Things with Ghouls/Wolvarines at the Sound of Music …
    Notes: Double-sided flier issued by the Berkeley record store Subterranean listing shows at a number of venues in the San Francisco area in April and May [1981]. The verso is an art/lyrics page created by the band Nervous Gender.
  - Suicidal Tendencies, 1984; 8.5 x 5.5 in. (Box 9, Folder 25)
    Additional bands or artists: Toy Dolls, Big Boys, Social Unrest, Stalag 13
    Main text: Goldenvoice presents - Way to go '84 - Suicidal Tendencies, Toy Dolls …
  - Suicidal Tendencies, 1984; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 25)
    Artist: Pushead
    Additional bands or artists: Toy Dolls, Big Boys, Social Unrest, [Stalag 13]
    Main text: Goldenvoice presents Suicidal Tendencies with Toy Dolls …
    Notes: A different flier for the same show as the above.
  - Sunday Painters, 1982; 29.75 x 19.75 in. (Box 40)
    Venue: [see note]
    Location: [Australia]
    Main text: Sunday Painters - Something to do - Try it once before you die
    Notes: Promotional poster for Australian band the Sunday Painters' 1982 album, with spraypainted text and ms. additions listing 3 gigs (at Tote, the Venetian Room, and the Marquee, likely all Australian venues).
  - Super Heroines, The, 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 25)
    Venue: Cathay de Grande and Al's Bar
    Additional bands or artists: Christian Death
    Main text: Get drunk & ignore the Super Heroines, June 5, 1982
  - Tapeworm, 1978; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 26)
    Location: [CT?]
    Main text: Hello Bob? Oh well, when he gets home, tell him about the new record by Tapeworm.
    Notes: Promotional flier for Tapeworm's 7" EP "Break My Face."
  - Teenage Jesus and the Jerks, 1978; 8.5 x 14 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    Venue: Max's Kansas City
    Additional bands or artists: Tina La Hotski, Blinding Headache
    Main text: Teenage Jesus and the Jerks
  - Television, 1974; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 26)
    Venue: CBGB
    Additional bands or artists: The Stillettoes
    Main text: Television and Stillettoes at C.B.G.B.
  - Television, 1975; 11 x 17 in. (Box 27, Folder 3)
    Main text: True life presents Television
    Notes: Signed by Richard Hell.
  - Three O'Clock, The, 1980s; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 26)
    Venue: Music Machine and the Roxy
    Main text: The Three O'Clock - Music Machine Feb 12, Roxy Feb 20
  - Toxic Shock, ca. 1980s; 8.5 x 5 in. (Box 9, Folder 26)
    Venue: Toxic Shock
    Main text: Toxic Shock - The syndrome to rely on …
    Notes: Flier for the record store Toxic Shock
  - Toxic Shock, ca. 1980s; 8.5 x 5.5 in. (Box 9, Folder 26)
    Main text: Toxic Shock - "Musik that matters" … Murder by tampon
  - Toy Dolls, 1984; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 26)
    Additional bands or artists: The Cult, The Meteors, MIA, The Breakouts
    Main text: July perks up! with two great shows 0 The Cult and the Meteors … Goldenvoice presents a blitzer! Toy Dolls and the Meteors …
  - Trouser Press (fanzine), ca. 1970s-80s; 17 x 11 in. (Box 30, Folder 2)
    Main text: Trouser Press
    Notes: Poster of badges for a variety of UK bands; likely originally issued as a stapled-in centerfold with an issue of Trouser Press
  - TSOL, 1981; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 26)
    Venue: Broadway Theatre
    Location: Santa Ana, CA
    Additional bands or artists: Social Distortion, China White, Verbal Abuse
    Main text: Rodent present - We wouldn't miss this concernt in the world! Actually we wanted to go but we went to Disneyland - Don't miss -- TSOL - True sounds of liberty …
  - TSOL, 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 26)
    Additional bands or artists: Bad Religion, The Massacre Guys, The Tourists
    Main text: Minors welcome - four bands - TSOL: True sounds of liberty - plus Bad Relgion ...
  - TSOL, 1982; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 26)
    Artist: Jaime [Hernandez?]
    Additional bands or artists: Angry Samoans, Agression, Jody Foster's Army, Articles of Faith, the Hated
    Main text: TSOL - Angry Samoans - Agression - P.U.N.X. - Nov. 20 …
  - TSOL, 1983; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 26)
    Venue: Gildersleeves
    Additional bands or artists: The Mob, The Abused, Undead, The Whore Lords
    Main text: Alexander-Hammer productions presents - Sun. March 20 - Alternative Tentacles/Faulty Recording Artist - TSOL
  - TSOL, 1980s; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 26)
    Additional bands or artists: Social Distortion, Red Beret, Misanthrops
    Main text: TSOL, [added in ms.: Social D], Red Beret, Masanthrops at Cathay de Grande …
    Notes: Social Distortion added to the bill in ms.
  - Tuxedomoon, 1979; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 26)
    Additional bands or artists: Levi & the Rockats, DOA, The Dils, Contracters, Alley Cats, Crime
    Main text: Sat. Sept. 1st - Tuxedomoon, Levi & te Rockats …
  - Tuxedomoon, 1979; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 26)
    Additional bands or artists: Levi & the Rockats, DOA
    Main text: Tuxedomoon, Levi & the Rockats, DOA - Saturday Sept. 1st …
    Notes: Different flier for the same performance as the above flier.
  - U.K. Decay, 1981; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 26)
    Additional bands or artists: Social Unrest, Wasted Youth
    Main text: Direct from England - U.K. Decay - Social Unrest - Wasted Youth
  - U.K. Subs, 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 26)
    Venue: Rock Hotel
    Additional bands or artists: Major Conflict, Chaos
    Main text: Welcome children!!! - U.K. Subs, Major Conflict - U.S. Chaos …
  - U.X.A., 1982; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 26)
    Additional bands or artists: Circle One, The Atoms, Isolations
    Main text: U.X.A. - Illusions of Grandeur - The original members - at Godzilla's
    Notes: Date corrected in ms. and/or stencil (originally listed as "Fri. Feb. 5").
  - V2, 1983; A4 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    Venue: Pips
    Location: [UK?]
    Additional bands or artists: Nervous Breakdown
    Main text: Pips new wave presents - Live - V2 - live - plus nervous breakdown - New wave disco …
  - Vandals, The, 1983; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 26)
    Venue: La Casa
    Main text: The Vandals - Saturday May 14 … Did I remember to turn off the stove?
  - Vandals, The, 1982; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 26)
    Venue: Bob's Place
    Additional bands or artists: Jody Foster's Army, The Atoms, Suicidal Tendencies
    Main text: Jimmy Woo presents Skank or Die '82 - The Vandals …
  - Vandals, The, 1982; 8.5 x 5.5 in. (Box 9, Folder 26)
    Additional bands or artists: Hated, Secret Hate, Shattered Faith
    Main text: The Galaxy presents - Friday, Dec. 10th - The Vandals + Hated …
  - Vandals, The, 1983; 8.5 x 5.5 in. (Box 9, Folder 26)
    Location: El Monte, CA
    Additional bands or artists: Mad Parade, Legion
    Main text: The Vandals - Wed June 29
  - Vice Squad, 1982; 8.5 x 5.5 in. (Box 9, Folder 26)
    Additional bands or artists: Chron Gen, Wasted Youth, Battalion of Saints, Channel 3, Circle One, Shattered Faith, Agression, Lost Cause, Bad Example, Deadly Reign
    Main text: Summer slam bands - Vice Squad, Chron Gen …
  - Virus, 1980s; 8.5 x 14 in. (Box 27, Folder 3)
    Additional bands or artists: Bad Posture
    Main text: Senseless murder - Don't eat meat - Don't wear fur - Extinction is forever
  - Vktms, 1977-1981; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 26)
    Main text: Vktms - Mabuhay Gardens - Jan. 1st
  - Vomit Pigs, The, 1979; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 26)
    Venue: D.J.'s
    Location: Dallas, TX
    Additional bands or artists: The Skuds, The Telefones, The Teenage Queers
    Main text: Dallas punk benefit show - the Vomit Pigs …
    Notes: With ms. note on bottom edge - "I think this flyer was made by Bobby Soxx"
  - Vs., 1979; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 26)
    Artist: Barrett
    Additional bands or artists: The Urge
    Main text: All girls and no sisters - The Bee Gees of the New Wave …
  - Vs., 1980; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 26)
    Venue: The Roosevelt
    Additional bands or artists: The Lewd, The Hostages
    Main text: Vs. - The Lewd - The Hostages
  - Waldorf Hysteria (club), 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 26)
    Venue: Waldorf Hysteria
    Main text: The night is young - rent the room - Bikini Waldorf - get the Waldorf Hysteria
    Notes: Advertising flier for the NY venue.
  - Wall of Voodoo, 1981; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 26)
    Additional bands or artists: Human Hands, Los Microwaves, Tuxedomoon
    Main text: From Los Angeles - Wall of Voodoo and Human Hands …
  - Wasted Youth, 1983; 8.5 x 5.5 in. (Box 9, Folder 26)
    Venue: Club Minimal
    Location: Sacramento, CA
    Additional bands or artists: Strawdogs, the Breakouts, Lockwork Range
    Main text: Clear & Distinct Ideas presents - L.A.'s Wasted Youth, Strawdogs, Breakouts, Lockwork Range and more?! …
  - Way-Outs, ca. 1970s-80s; 8.5 x 8.7 in. (Box 9, Folder 26)
    Main text: Way-Outs
    Notes: Generic promotional flier; band's name and photo with no additional information.
  - Weirdos, ca. 1980s; 11 x 17 in. (Box 27, Folder 3)
    Artist: Goldberg (photographs)
    Main text: Weirdos
  - Weirdos, ca. 1980s; 13.25 x 9.75 in. (Box 27, Folder 3)
    Main text: The Weirdos at Starwood
    Notes: Date on poster is simply "Jun"; likely used for multiple performances during a residence.
  - Weirdos, The, 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 26)
    Main text: Weirdos - Thursday Dec. 20 1979 - at the Whisky